So we moved here in 1963.
There was nothing here on the property.
We had a camp across the creek until we had this bridge behind me built in 63, 64.
And then after we got the bridge done, we built the little cabin that's behind Jaemyun.
I don't know if you can see it yet.
for that that was built in like '64.
We had no electricity, no water.
We just had a tent on a platform.
Took down the platform, or the tent,
and built the little house.
And then we still didn't have electricity or water,
but we managed to use a headlight and a battery for lights.
And then we just used buckets, I guess, or bottles for water until we had a spring built that was up on the hill that we built
and we had water midway through summer and then we ran out.
And then we added onto the cabin three times!
And then in 1990, we built the big house
and that's where mom and dad lived.
And then when they passed, Gene and Patty had moved up here. to take care of the property
and now he is my caretaker of the property
and he's doing a great job.
And it's been a great place to have, to be raised and grow up
and have all this to ourselves.
So it's been a blessing.
We used to have a dam under the creek
and we would, as kids, we would all have inner tubes and air mattresses
and we would play in the creek all afternoon till we were like blue-lipped.
and it we finally came out
and we could only get in the creek after we got our chores done in the morning
and then in the afternoon we could play in the creek
so it was a lot a lot of fun
and i'm grateful that we have this property
and Jaemyun and to do this little video and Kelly and the other little kids that are running around here
so it's been  a treat
can you explain the why the people called the The Dry Creek here?
The creek itself is called Dry Creek, not because it ran dry of water, because when back in the 1800s or 1890s, whenever it was, the gold rush was going on, they never found any gold in the creek,
so they named it Dry Creek,
and that's how it's got his name.
And then our creek, Dry Creek, feeds a lake downstream
called Collins Lake,
and it's a pretty good-sized lake.
It's known for fishing.
they stock it like three times a year
which is good
the cabin was built in mid 60s early 60s
and it was just the front part
and that's where we stayed
uh my mom and dad and Gary, Gene, Sue and myself
we just stayed in that front part of the cabin
and then through the years it got added on to three times
and then in 2007, I think it was,
we had a water line break
and it flooded the whole place.
Nobody was up here
and the water ran for three weeks.
So we had to strip it right down the inside,
strip it all the way down to the studs so the building would dry out and wouldn't get moldy.
And then it became storage area
and then in Today our year is 2026,
so in 2023... I started rebuilding it
and I put all new electrical in it
and all new plumbing, siding, windows,
and just rebuild it so
I could stay in there and live
and be happy.
So if he goes over here, you can see the back deck and the porch and the back part of the cabin, which is nice.
So we call that the cabin
and then the other, the house over here,
we just call it the big house.
And that's where we have all of our dinners and everything.
What's the difference between the house and cabin?
Just because this was a cabin.
We stayed in for a long time.
Mom had to sleep upstairs, and she fell down the stairs,
so they had to build the house to make it level
As they were getting up in age and didn't have to worry about falls anymore.
And the cabin is small. The house is big.
Big, okay. Yeah.
And then my mom's memorial bell.
I don't know if they got a picture of that yet,
but that's right behind them here.
Right behind you.
See the the thing up on the top?
That was my mom's memorial bell that we built and this was mining equipment that we found up in the hills.
We used to go exploring up there, some of the old mines and everything,
and this is just some of the stuff that we picked up.
The bell is actually from Depoe Bay in Oregon.
And I found that,
so that's when I made the memorial bell for mom.
when did you make it when did you make it
Must have been 2006.
2006. Yeah. Almost 20 years ago. Yeah. Yeah.
Almost or is?
Yeah.
Anyway, that's all I got.
You know, this is the area that we have and grew up on.
And now Jaemyun and Kelly get to enjoy it
and the kids too.
Yeah. All right.
Thank you.
Who are you?
I'm Wayne.
Uncle Wayne, as the kids call me.
Okay, thank you.